



+60182796846



nurizziana.ishak@gmail.com



Nur Izziana Ishak

SKILL & COMPETENCIES

Technical Skills

MS Words : Excellent

MS Excel : Excellent

MS PowerPoint : Excellent

Aspen Plus : Good

MATLAB : Good

Soft Skills

Leadership : Excellent

Communication : Excellent

Teamwork : Excellent

Organization : Good

Management : Good

NUR IZZIANA BINTI ISHAK

A fresh graduate of chemical engineering who is seeking an opportunity for employment. An enthusiastic person that have high interest and ability to excel. I want to give maximum contribution to organization while developing my potential and capabilities to the highest point possible. In 5 years, I would be an expert and give more contribution in engineering field using knowledge and experience

| Flexible | Optimist | Passionate | Independently but effectively work in team |

EDUCATION

Bachelors Degree of Chemical Engineering (2013-2017)

Universiti Malaysia Pahang

CGPA: 2.86/4.00

Matriculation Programme (2011-2013)

Kolej Matrikulasi Pulau Pinang

CGPA: 3.46/4.00

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (2006-2010)

SMK Jitra

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Receptionist (August 2017- now)

Mimilala Boutique Hotel & Homestay, Shah Alam, Selangor Tasks:

- Greet, assist and direct customers
- Answer all incoming call and handle caller's inquire
- Update bookings and allotment online
- Ensure all guest check in, check out, request and inquiries promptly and efficiently
- Duties of housekeeping

Engineer Trainee (Jun 2016- September 2016)

SUJPlas Sdn Bhd, Kemaman, Terengganu Tasks:

- Assign in production line
- Conduct daily data recording activities in production line.
- Perform QC inspection according to quality requirement
- Provide immediate feedback to production supervisor on detected part which out of specification
- Review and optimize quality of FIBC bag
- Design and develop new design according customer's specification
- Any other duties assigned by supervisor

LANGUAGES

Malay Languages

Speaking : Excellent
Writing : Excellent

Reading : Excellent

Soft Skills

Speaking : Excellent

Writing : Excellent

Reading : Excellent

REFERENCES

Dr Sunarti Bt Abdul Rahman

Academic Advisor Faculty of Chemical Engineering and Resources,

Universiti Malaysia Pahang

+60139879141

sunarti@ump.edu.my

YH Dato' Jeffrey Khor Chooi Beng

Director of Career Placement & Development Centre and Industry Partnership & Community Relation Department,

Universiti Malaysia Pahang

+60136251018

jeffreykhor@ump.edu.my

CURRICULUM & ACHIEVEMENT

Committee member of KOR-SISPA

2016 - Organize Seminar Kebangsaan KOR-SISPA and be

Secretariat of Food and Beverages

Joined Majlis Pertauliahan & Perhimpunan Kebangsaan KOR-SISPA and be participant in

2015 - Explorace SISPA Civil Defence Challenge at USM

2014 - Rescue Challenge at UKM

Attend course that organized by *Angkatan Pertahanan Awam* (APM)

2016 - Methodology & Coaching Course

2014 - Ascending & Descending Course

2013 - Basic Trauma & Life Support Course

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCES

Flood Volunteers

2014 – Cook and distribute food to flood victim at SMK Pandan

- Help flood victim in cleaning their house at Kampung Kurnia

2013 - Help in packaging basic need for flood victim at UMP

- Help flood victim in cleaning their house at Sunga Isap

FINAL YEAR PROJECT

Title: Evaluation of Strong Anion Exchange Hypercrosslinked Resin for Lanthanum Removal

Objectives: To study the pH stability of strong anion exchange hypercrosslinked resin and to evaluate the resin using batch method for removal lanthanum

CAPSTONE PROJECT (PLANT DESIGN)

Title: Production of Hydrogen from Palm Oil Biomass

Objectives: The project was projected to produces 45 000 MT of hydrogen from palm oil biomass with the aim fulfilling the demand of Malaysia